

CONTACTS

+38 098 461 7282



www.chorny-alexander/

in <u>Alexander Chorny</u>

Vinnitsa, Ukraine

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
 - responsive
 - valid
 - cross-browser
- JavaScript
 - React
- Figma, Photoshop
- Git

LANGUAGES

- English Upper-Intermediate
- German Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

ALEXANDER CHORNY

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a developer with good experience with HTML, CSS and JS. I strive to create reliable, adaptive, cross-browser web products based on best practices and accessibility.

In life, I enjoy self-learning and therefore I try to develop, both in terms of technical skills and communication skills. So I plan my days to improve my frontend development skills, learn and use tools to speed up web development and improve my language skills (English and German).

I feel the need to learn anything new or do something useful in a day. Moreover I like doing sports and developing in various directions: swimming, running, strength training.

EXPERIENCE

jan 2023 - up to now

Freelance Web Developer

I am currently working on two projects:

- 1. ONE-OF-PRO (Tech Job Platform) teamwork;
- 2. MYHOBBY-ECOMMERSE (store) I work independently.

In these two projects, I use and master different technologies, languages and frameworks such as: React \cdot Next.js \cdot Docker \cdot TypeScript \cdot GraphQL \cdot MongoDB \cdot Jest \cdot GitHub/Codespaces \cdot GitHub/task-board.

jul 2009 - feb 2022

MYHOBBY

Consultant/Content Manager

Website maintenance, consultations, sales, purchase of goods.

apr 2015 - jun 2015 APPAREL EXPRESS

Improvement Of A Website

Improvement of website design and functionality. Refinement of the order sorting module.

dec 2014 - feb 2015 KRAINEVA ANASTASIA

Website Development

Website development for an artist.

EDUCATION

November 2022 - up to now | USA JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures FreeCodeCamp

September 2022 - November 2022 | USA Responsive Web Design FreeCodeCamp

September 1991 - May 1994 | Ukraine (Vinnitsa)

Maintenance of electrical installations

Vocational and Technical Education Center No. 1